What attracted me to Tessl was when I was first introduced
to the philosophy that, hey, these document specifications,
this plain text context is now going to drive the new age of programming.
Something about that really resonated.
It's been a really good experience.
The people here are lovely, and I think that that helps me work a little bit.
I like being personable with other people.
I like talking to people.
I like coming into the office.
I like interacting with others.
the calibre of the team is very high.
So I think we have an incredibly rich and experienced team.
And something that really stood out to me was that considering a team
that has so much experience and has worked in many different fields of engineering
before, the amount of openness to change and the amount of willingness
to actually try new technologies and try different things, was really high.
And so we get not only the experience of some incredible engineers
that have worked on some complex systems before,
but then pair that with a willingness to try different things
that pair really well with this environment right now.
The thing that, for me, has set the culture here
apart by far over other places that I've worked at
is a combination of the incredibly high trust and high autonomy.
I think that that very clearly sets the culture apart.
I don't have to seek any approval to actually go and work
on a solution to a problem that I think is genuinely meaningful, right?
If I see something myself and I have the time and the resources,
I can go and work on it myself, and the team is always receptive to these ideas.
We have multiple people that have shipped multiple things in the last few months
that were not on our roadmap,
that came and were born out of an idea or intuition that they have.
the leadership have created a culture
where everyone's intuition is very clearly valued.
I would love to still be here in five years.
I see myself here growing a lot more into the sort of work that I want to do,
specifically from the perspective of product and engineering
and driving solutions to meaningful problems in our space.
Hopefully we've had a massive impact on our industry in five years.
That'd be awesome.